<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="slogan">Help us make Genoa even more Green!</string>
    <string name="e_questo">Where do I throw this?</string>
    <string name="dove_lo_butto">Where do I throw this?</string>
    <string name="scopri">DISCOVER</string>
    <string name="rifiuti_pericolosi">Dangerous waste</string>
    <string name="spedizioni">Expeditions</string>
    <string name="versione">Beta Version 1.0</string>
    <string name="impostazioni">Settings</string>
    <string name="lingua">Language</string>
    <string name="notifiche">Notifications</string>
    <string name="logout">Exit</string>
    <string name="RUP_tit">"Hazardous Municipal Waste and Bulky Waste "</string>
    <string name="rif_pericolisi_descrizione">Hazardous municipal waste (RUP) is the type of waste produced by domestic users which, by containing a high dose of substances dangerous to the environment and health, they must be collected separately in order to permit their regular treatment and disposal at the approved facilities.</string>
    <string name="RUP_but">FIND THE NEAREST COLLECTION CENTRE</string>
    <string name="log">Don’t you have an account yet?</string>
    <string name="SearchViewButtoHint">Looking for a product</string>
    <string name="infoAssistenza">Support</string>
    <string name="infoCondividi">Share</string>
    <string name="infoSeguici">Follow us on Social Media!</string>
    <string name="password_dimenticata">Forgot password?</string>
    <string name="accedi">Log in</string>
    <string name="registrati_ora">Register now!</string>
    <string name="recupera_la_tua_password">Retrieve your password</string>
    <string name="annulla">CANCEL</string>
    <string name="invia">SEND</string>
    <string name="visualizza_la_mappa_di_tutti_i_centri_di_raccolta_rifiuti_a_genova">See the map of all waste collection centers in Genoa:</string>
    <string name="o_cerca_il_centro_di_raccolta_in_base_al_prodotto_che_hai_da_smaltire">Or look for the collection center based on the product you have to dispose of:</string>
    <string name="rifiuti_ingombranti">BULKY WASTE</string>
    <string name="pile_e_batterie_esauste">SPENT BATTERIES</string>
    <string name="olio_esausto_e_filtri_olio">SPENT OIL AND OIL FILTERS</string>
    <string name="scegli_un_luogo_sulla_mappa">Choose a location on the map:</string>
    <string name="le_spedizioni_a_cui_parteciperai">The shipments in which you will participate:</string>
    <string name="aggiungi_una_nuova_spedizione">Add a new shipment</string>
    <string name="le_spedizioni_create_da_te">Shipments created by you:</string>
    <string name="le_mie_spedizioni">MY OWN CONSIGNMENTS</string>
    <string name="partecipa_ad_una_delle_seguenti_spedizioni_di_volontariato">Take part in one of the following voluntary expeditions:</string>
    <string name="accedi_subito">Log in now!</string>
    <string name="hai_gi_un_account">Do you already have an account?</string>
    <string name="conferma">Confirm</string>
    <string name="farmaci_scaduti_e_contenitori">EXPIRED MEDICINES AND CONTAINERS</string>
    <string name="vernici_solventi_e_insetticidi">PAINTS, SOLVENTS AND INSECTICIDES</string>
    <string name="registrazione">REGISTRATION</string>
    <string name="ripeti_password">Repeat password</string>
    <string name="rec_pass">Enter your email here and we’ll send you the link to change your account password</string>
    <string name="move_map_instruction">Move the map and select the desired location.</string>
    <string name="user_location_permission_explanation">This function requires location permissions to work</string>
    <string name="user_location_permission_not_granted">You don\'t have tracking permissions.</string>
    <string name="exit">Are you sure you want to exit?</string>
    <string name="segnala">Report</string>
    <string name="nessun_prodotto_trovato">No product found.</string>
    <string name="popup_impostazioni">Are you sure you want to log out?</string>
    <string name="logout_toast">Logout happened with success.</string>
    <string name="login_successo">Login happened with success.</string>
    <string name="verifica_email">Please check your email address.</string>
    <string name="riprova">Retry.</string>
    <string name="login_storto">Something went wrong with the login.</string>
    <string name="no_campi_vuoti">There can be no empty fields.</string>
    <string name="errore_db">Database error.</string>
    <string name="si">Yes</string>
    <string name="gps_non_attivo">This function requires the use of GPS. Do you want to enable it?</string>
    <string name="seleziona_un_luogo">Select a location</string>
    <string name="email_inviata">Email sent</string>
    <string name="registrazione_avvenuta">Successful registration. Check your email for verification.</string>
    <string name="registrazione_storta">Something went wrong with the recording.</string>
    <string name="username_in_uso">Username already in use.</string>
    <string name="pass_confermapass_non_coincidono">Password and Confirm password do not match.</string>
    <string name="pass_min_6_caratteri">The password must have at least 6 characters.</string>
    <string name="nessuna_spedizione_trovata">No shipment found yet.</string>
    <string name="elimina">Delete</string>
    <string name="scegliere_la_posizione">Choose the location</string>
    <string name="non_partecipare">Not to join</string>
    <string name="impostare_data">Set date:</string>
    <string name="data">date</string>
    <string name="ora">time</string>
    <string name="impostare_ora">Set time:</string>
    <string name="breve_descrizione">Short description:</string>
    <string name="aggiungi">ADD</string>
    <string name="inserisci_qui_una_breve_descrizione_sul_lavoro_da_compiere">Enter here a short description of the work to be done.</string>
    <string name="posizione">Location:</string>
    <string name="indietro">Back</string>
    <string name="partecipa">Join</string>
    <string name="numero_partecipanti">Number of Participants:</string>
    <string name="data_e_ora">Date/time:</string>
    <string name="organizzatore">Organizer:</string>
    <string name="location_picker_dropped_marker_snippet_no_results">No result</string>
    <string name="location_picker_select_location_button_cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="location_picker_select_location_button_select">Select a location</string>
    <string name="popup_sped2">Are you sure you want to delete the expedition?</string>
    <string name="popup_sped1">Are you sure you don’t want to join in the expedition anymore?</string>
    <string name="informazioni">Informations</string>
    <string name="consulta_la_sezione_dedicata">Consult the relative section</string>
    <string name="inizia">START</string>
    <string name="modifica_profilo">Edit profile</string>
    <string name="modifica_password">Change password:</string>
    <string name="modifica_nome_utente">Change username:</string>
    <string name="salta">SKIP</string>
    <string name="crea_una_spedizione1">Create a shipment</string>
    <string name="utilizza_questa_funzione_per_trovare_subito_il_giusto_cassonetto_per_ogni_rifiuto">Use this feature to quickly find the right dumpster for every waste.</string>
    <string name="trova_la_stazione_ecologica_pi_vicina_a_te_per_i_vari_rifiuti_speciali">Find the nearest ecological station to you for various special waste.</string>
    <string name="organizzati_con_vari_gruppi_di_volontariato_per_bonificare_il_verde_del_nostro_territorio">Organized with various voluntary groups to clean up the green of our territory.</string>
    <string name="richiedi">Request via email</string>
    <string name="inserire_email">Enter valid email</string>
    <string name="pericolo1_tit">Dangerous waste</string>
    <string name="pericolo2_tit">Electronic devices</string>
    <string name="pericolo3_tit">Cooking oil</string>
    <string name="pericolo4_tit">Batteries and medicines</string>
    <string name="pericolo5_tit">Toner and cartridges</string>
    <string name="pericolo1_desc">
        <br> Some types of waste are defined as hazardous due to the consequences they may have on human health and the surrounding environment. \n \n </br>
        <br> Collecting them in a differentiated way, in addition to recovery purposes, therefore has an important objective of safeguarding and protecting safety. \n \n </br>
        <br> - Waste oils (including containers) of mineral or synthetic origin, used for engines and machines, or of vegetable origin. They are very polluting, if dispersed in the environment they infiltrate the ground and can contaminate the aquifers \n </br>
        <br> - Toxic and flammable: they are labeled T and / or F. They can seriously compromise the health of people and animals \n </br>
        <br> - Household chemicals (including containers), detergents, insecticides, moths, chemical products for photography, ethyl and denatured alcohol, bathroom cleaners, trichlorethylene, polishing products, descalers, chemical fertilizers, herbicides, fungicides, disinfectants, acids and chemical solutions \n </br>
        <br> - Paints and solvents (including containers): paints, varnishes, solvents, paint removers, adhesives, fillers, sealants, stain removers, polishes, rust inhibitors \n </br>
        <br> - Thermometers \n </br>
        <br> - Neon and light bulbs: neon tubes, halogen lamps, fluorescent lamps \n \n </br>
        What can you do with hazardous waste \n \n
        <br> - take them to the Ecological Islands: Amiu staff collect them free of charge and send them for disposal \n </br>
        <br> - take them directly to the recovery platforms in Genoa \n </br>
        <br> - deliver them to the Ecovan + pickup truck, which operates weekly in the city streets at set times and days. \n \n </br>
        What you CANNOT do with hazardous waste \n \n
        <br> - Abandon them on the street and next to the waste bins \n </br>
        <br> - Put them in waste collection containers \n </br>
        <br> - Put them in containers for separate waste collection \n </br>
        <br> - Disassemble and separate parts of household appliances, batteries, toner containers for printers, heat or burn them. </br>
    </string>
    <string name="pericolo5_desc">
        <br> The cartridges used in laser, inkjet, needle printers and drum units for photocopiers are waste to be collected separately and should not be thrown into the unsorted waste bin. \n\n </br>
        <br> Those of domestic origin can be taken free of charge to the Ecological Islands, to the Ecovan + trucks set up for the collection of bulky and dangerous waste and small WEEE.  \n\n </br>
        <br> Freelancers and companies, as long as they are registered in the National Register of Environmental Managers in category 2 bis, can take their cartridges and toners to the Ecological Islands and Ecovan + trucks without filling in the waste identification and transport form, if you do not exceeds the daily quantity of 30 kg or 30 liters and if no more than 5 contributions are made per calendar year. \n\n </br>
        <br> Beyond the fifth contribution in the calendar year, those who need it will have to register with the register (if they have the right) and will have to fill out the form to deliver the waste.  \n\n </br>
        <br> Alternatively, they can take advantage of a customized collection service for a fee by writing to contacts@amiu.genova.it or by calling 010 80 89 800. In this way the cartridges and toner will be reused thus extending their life cycle.  </br>
    </string>
    <string name="pericolo4_desc">
        <br> Batteries and drugs are hazardous waste that should NOT be thrown into the bin. In fact, they contain pollutants that must not end up in landfills or dispersed in the environment. \n\n  </br>
        <br> Used batteries of all types (stylus, torch, tablet, etc.) are hazardous waste as they consist of heavy metals such as mercury, cadmium, nickel and lead. Thanks to the separate collection, they are treated and disposed of in special plants. \n\n </br>
        <br> Find containers for the separate collection of batteries in supermarkets, shops and affiliated resellers (tobacconists, appliance stores, etc.).  \n\n </br>
        <br> Batteries and drugs can also be brought free of charge to Ecovan + and after specific treatment, they will be disposed of properly, thus avoiding damage to the environment. </br>
    </string>
    <string name="pericolo3_desc">
        <br> It has been calculated that 160 million kilos of exhausted vegetable oil from households are produced in Italy every year. This is the oil from frying, canned tuna or that contained in the jars of preserves or leftover from the salad.  \n\n </br>
        <br> Often the oil is not separated correctly, but thrown into the sink, with considerable damage from both an economic and environmental point of view. If introduced into the sewer system, it ends up in the municipal purifier which, to treat a kilo of oil, uses at least 3 kw / h of energy and costs about 50 cents. \n\n  </br>
        <br> Used oil, if properly sorted, is recyclable and, moreover, it is a precious resource: from a kilo of oil, in fact, it is possible to obtain biofuel with low environmental impact or glycerin for the cosmetic industry. In Genoa this type of oil is collected: in the ecological islands, by the EcoVan + truck (see the appointments). \n\n  </br>
        <br> Through the Riciclolio project, co-financed by the Life + Community Program, the oil collection system has been expanded through the installation of special containers distributed in schools, neighborhood associations and meeting points. \n\n  </br>
        <br> Citizens have these points at their disposal to bring used oil which will then be collected and sent for recycling.  \n\n </br>
        <br> It is important to remember that these containers are used only for the collection of edible oil from home and it is forbidden to insert motor oil (that of the machines and that can be delivered to the ecological islands and on the EcoVan + truck.   </br>
    </string>
    <string name="pericolo2_desc">
        <br> What are WEEE? Electric and electronic appliances that are powered by electricity, by connecting them to the home socket or with batteries, no longer working that we want to throw away.  \n\n </br>
        <br> Here is an example of the main WEEE:  \n\n </br>
        <br> televisions, food processors, toasters, microwave ovens, computers, modems, mobile phones, utensils, toys powered by batteries or batteries or electric wires, clocks, refrigerators, washing machines and other household appliances.  \n\n </br>
        <br> According to their characteristics, they are divided into 5 categories: \n\n  </br>
        <br> - R1: Cold and climate (eg refrigerators and air conditioners, air conditioning appliances \n </br>
        <br> - R2: Large whites (eg washing machines, dishwashers, microwave ovens, range cookers) \n </br>
        <br> - R3: TVs and monitors (televisions, computer monitors) \n </br>
        <br> - R4: Information technology, consumer electronics and small household appliances (e.g. vacuum cleaners, sewing machines, irons, fryers, blenders, computers (central unit, mouse, keyboard), printers, fax machines, mobile phones, video recorders, radios, ceiling lights)  </br>
        <br> - R5: Light sources (e.g. neon, low consumption lamps - N.B. old incandescent bulbs are not WEEE and must be thrown in unsorted waste) \n \n </br>
        <br> Where do I throw the WEEE? For a correct collection of WEEE the first thing to do is to separate the waste. AMIU offers several free services to help you differentiate them, WEEE: \n \n </br>
        <br> - They can be taken to ecological islands (all types of WEEE) \n </br>
        <br> - They can be taken to EcoVan (all types of WEEE) \n </br>
        <br> For large appliances (refrigerators, kitchens, televisions, ...) it is also possible to request the home collection service for a fee. The stores that sell electrical and electronic equipment (EEE) also collaborate in the collection, in different ways: when you buy a new equipment, take the old one to your shopkeeper who can collect it for free. This obligation applies to all businesses that distribute EEE of any kind, even in the case of teleshopping, online sales or home delivery. \n \n </br>
        <br> In addition, the new WEEE legislation has introduced the 1 against 0 obligation for large distributors. Consumers can deliver small WEEE - less than 25 cm - free of charge to large points of sale, with a sales area of ​​electrical and electronic equipment exceeding 400 square meters, without any obligation to purchase. Even small shops can decide to join this initiative on a voluntary basis. \n \n </br>
        <br> Why separate WEEE? From a TV you get ferrous metals (48%), plastic (21%), printed circuits (9.8%), glass (8%) and more. From small appliances recycled correctly we can obtain plastic for garden or printed accessories, copper for new taps and even silver, palladium, gold and aluminum. \n \n </br>
        <br> Collecting and recycling them correctly means: \n \n </br>
        <br> - Reduce CO2 emissions: because we reduce greenhouse gases and the substances contained are eliminated safely. \n </br>
        <br> - Saving energy: because today recycling consumes less energy than what is needed to extract raw materials. \n </br>
        <br> - Recovering raw materials from waste: because aluminum, glass, copper and plastic can be largely reused. \n\n </br>
        <br> - Fighting the illegal trafficking of electronic devices to developing countries: because in the poorest countries they are not recycled properly, polluting and increasing child labor. </br>
    </string>
    <string name="differenziata1_desc">
        <br> Paper is composed of cellulosic fibers normally present in nature. These, through chemical processes, once dust, dyes and adhesives have been eliminated, can be re-aggregated again and then recycled. Properly recycling paper allows you to recover materials and benefit the environment. \n\n </br>
        <br> To recycle paper: \n \n </br>
        <br> - Use only the white containers \n </br>
        <br> - Minimize clutter: folding newspapers, crushing cardboard boxes to reduce their volume and using paper bags \n </br>
        <br> - Do not put the card in plastic bags. This lowers the quality of the collected material and increases the costs of recycling \n </br>
        YOU CAN INTRODUCE IN THE WHITE CONTATINER (ATTENTION: to comply with the regulations the container for paper throughout the city will become BLUE. The containers will be progressively replaced.) \n\n
        <br> - Paper and cardboard of all sizes \n </br>
        <br> - Non-laminated newspapers, magazines and advertising brochures \n </br>
        <br> - Books and notebooks \n </br>
        <br> - Paper for graphic, drawing and photocopying uses \n </br>
        <br> - Beverage carton (eg Tetra Pak for milk, fruit juices, cream) \n </br>
        <br> - Paper bags \n </br>
        <br> - Boxes and packaging in paper, cardboard, corrugated cardboard and wrapping paper \n </br>
        DO NOT PUT INTO THE WHITE CONTAINER \n \n
        <br> Dirty paper (eg used napkins and paper plates), greaseproof paper for food, absorbent paper for kitchen and baking paper, plasticized paper, diapers, chemical paper for fax and carbonless, polystyrene and plastic bags. When possible, reduce the volumes. </br>
    </string>
    <string name="differenziata1_tit">Paper and cardboard</string>
    <string name="differenziata2_desc">
        <br> Glass is a material obtained by melting a mixture of silica sand, soda (sodium carbonate) and limestone at very high temperatures (about 1,500 degrees). If abandoned in the environment, glass degrades over a very long time, while it can be recycled over and over again. Recycling glass means collecting it separately, crushing it and mixing it with more soda and limestone, melting it at much lower temperatures than those required with virgin material. This allows considerable energy and economic savings on the extraction and melting phases of raw materials. \n \n </br>
        <br> To recycle glass: \n \n </br>
        <br> - Use only green containers \n </br>
        <br> - Do not introduce ceramics and porcelain: these materials have a different melting point and can damage large quantities of glass during processing \n </br>
        <br> - Introduce glass free from any foreign material into the bells: caps, labels, lids. They must be recycled individually depending on the material \n </br>
        <br> - Prefer the glass packaging as a returnable empty: it allows a saving of raw materials and energy \n \n </br>
        YOU CAN PUT into the GREEN container \n \n
        <br> - Bottles and glasses \n </br>
        <br> - Jars, jars and glass containers of any color, without cap \n \n </br>
        DO NOT PUT into the GREEN container \n \n
        <br> Ceramics and porcelain (whole or broken crockery), mirrors, window glass, wired glass, neon bulbs and tubes, TV screens and monitors, jars with remnants of colors or paints, different materials such as crystals \n \n </br>
        <br> Please note: The packaging must not be washed, to avoid bad smells just rinse it quickly, the labels must not be removed, but the residues must be removed. </br>
    </string>
    <string name="differenziata2_tit">Glass</string>
    <string name="differenziata3_desc">
        <br> Over 30% of household waste is made up of organic waste, i.e. food waste and both raw and cooked food scraps, fruit, vegetables, foliage, cut plants, weeds, etc. \n \n </br>
        <br> If properly treated, they can become an excellent fertilizer for the plants on our terrace or for the vegetable garden and garden. AMIU is extending the separate collection of organic waste (with brown street container) in the different neighborhoods. \n \n </br>
        <br> The wet waste collected is destined for treatment plants that produce natural fertilizer for crops and allow renewable energy to be recovered through the production of biogas. \n \n </br>
        <br> For a quality recovery, however, it is necessary that the rules of separate collection are well observed to prevent foreign materials from ending up in the brown containers. \n \n </br>
        WHAT TO INTRODUCE in the BROWN container \n \n
        <br> - Food leftovers (both raw and cooked), peels, seeds, cores and stones of fruit, vegetables \n </br>
        <br> - Meat, fish, cheese, bread, pasta, eggs, coffee grounds and tea bags \n </br>
        <br> - Dried fruit shells, egg shells, fish bones, hair and feathers, mollusc shells \n </br>
        <br> - Kitchen paper, paper napkins and handkerchiefs, wooden matches, corks, sawdust \n </br>
        <br> - Grass, foliage, small plants and cut flowers \n \n </br>
        <br> Please note: do not insert bags and plastic bags, use only compostable or paper bags \n \n </br>
        <br> DOMESTIC COMPOSTING. Like the farmers who have always used this technique to fertilize the earth, even those who have a garden or a terrace in the city can produce themselves an excellent fertilizer for plants and vegetables, and at the same time help reduce the amount of waste sent to landfills. . \n </br>
        <br> Thanks to an initiative carried out in collaboration with the Department of the Environment of the Municipality of Genoa, anyone who undertakes to practice home composting and has the necessary requirements (a garden, vegetable garden or terrace of at least 15 square meters) can obtain a discount on TARI: 10 euros for a single user, 15 euros for a family with two or more members. </br>
    </string>
    <string name="differenziata3_tit">Organic wet</string>
    <string name="differenziata4_desc">
        <br> Lo StaccaPanni is not the usual collection of used clothes and clothes. It is a path in which each stage contributes to the development of a culture of solidarity and attention to others. \n \n  </br>
        <br> The collection and selection of material represent a job opportunity for people belonging to weak social groups. The clothes in good condition are distributed to families and people in difficulty through the Auxilium foundation circuit. \n \n </br>
        <br> But the donated clothes are more than what is requested. What is left over is therefore sold to companies specialized in the used clothing sector. In this way, the dress is not thrown into landfills and is transformed into revenue that is spent in favor of marginalized people in Genoa in projects indicated by the Diocesan Caritas of Genoa. The proceeds from the clothes stand, for example, help to cover the costs for the canteen for homeless people at the Casa della Giovane in Piazza Santa Sabina in Genoa (more than 2,400 meals a month). \n \n </br>
        YOU CAN INTRODUCE INTO THE MACHINE: \n \n
        <br> Used clothes and clothing, shoes, bags and hats, blankets and linen in general packed in closed bags. </br>
    </string>
    <string name="differenziata4_tit">Used clothes</string>
    <string name="differenziata5_desc">
        <br> Plastic is obtained from petroleum through a process called polymerization, ie the binding of some molecules with identical others in theoretically infinite chains, by heating in the presence of catalysts. Plastic is strong, waterproof, lightweight and economical. However, it has a big flaw: it is not biodegradable and therefore very polluting, so it must be completely recycled. \n \n </br>
        <br> Plastic has little weight and a lot of volume, so bottles and containers generally need to be kept as small as possible. \n \n </br>
        <br> In general, all plastic containers, even those for food (as long as they are free of residues), should be rinsed and crushed, closed with their cap, which is also recyclable, and placed in the yellow container for collecting plastic. \n </br>
        <br> There is no need to peel off any paper labels. \n \n </br>
        <br> To recycle plastic: \n </br>
        <br> - Use only the yellow containers \n </br>
        <br> - Reduce the footprint of bottles and packaging \n </br>
        <br> - Avoid the presence of foreign bodies \n </br>
        <br> - Do not leave rubbish outside or around collection containers \n \n </br>
        YOU CAN INTRODUCE into the YELLOW container: \n \n
        <br> - Plates and glasses in plastic \n </br>
        <br> - Bottles and plastic bottles for water, soft drinks and food products \n </br>
        <br> - Jars for food products (eg yoghurt, desserts), packaging and plastic trays for food \n </br>
        <br> - Plastic packaging for eggs and other shaped plastic packaging \n </br>
        <br> - Bags and plastic bags for food products (eg pasta, bread, crackers, frozen foods), nets for fruit and vegetables \n </br>
        <br> - Bottles for household detergents and detergents, dispensers for personal hygiene and cosmetics \n </br>
        <br> - Plastic bags, bags and boxes, nylon and cellophane bags, cellophane film, plastic caps, plant pots (without soil) \n </br>
        <br> - Polystyrene trays and trays (for fruit, vegetables, meat), packaging of small polystyrene appliances \n </br>
        <br> - Coat hangers \n \n </br>
        DO NOT INTRODUCE into the YELLOW container: \n\n
        <br> Fruit and vegetable crates made of plastic; plastic cutlery; toys; cases for CDs, DVDs and other audiovisual materials; durable plastic goods (household appliances, household items, furnishing accessories, etc.); all plastic waste soiled with organic materials or dangerous substances such as paint, glues, etc .; hospital waste (eg syringes, plasma bags, containers for physiological fluids and for hemodialysis); containers for paints, enamels, stain removers, acids, glues and insecticides \n \n </br>
        <br> Please note: The packaging must not be washed, to avoid bad smells just rinse it quickly, the labels must not be removed, but food residues must be removed. And when possible, reduce the volumes. </br>
    </string>
    <string name="differenziata5_tit">Plastic</string>
    <string name="differenziata6_desc">
        <br> Aluminum combined with silicon, magnesium, copper, zinc and manganese form numerous light alloys, which are used in modern technology. Pure aluminum is instead used as a conductor in high voltage lines. \n \n </br>
        <br> Steel is an alloy based on iron and carbon in different quantities depending on the purpose. It is the most recycled material in the world: steel for vehicles, household appliances, rails, rods for construction, bridge beams are produced from scrap. \n \n </br>
        <br> To recycle metals: \n </br>
        <br> - Use only the yellow containers \n </br>
        <br> - Rinse the food trays and eliminate any food residues \n </br>
        <br> - Crumple the aluminum foil so that it does not disperse \n </br>
        <br> - Put the cans marked AL \n </br> into the container
        <br> - Do not leave rubbish around the containers \n \n </br>
        YOU CAN INTRODUCE into the YELLOW container: \n \n
        <br> - Cans for drinks and oil \n </br>
        <br> - Aluminum kitchen foil, chocolate wrappers and yogurt lids \n </br>
        <br> - Tin cans for food (eg tomatoes, meat, tuna, legumes, pet food) \n </br>
        <br> - Aluminum trays and containers for storing and freezing food \n </br>
        <br> - Spray cans for deodorants, hair sprays or whipped cream \n </br>
        <br> - Metal tins and boxes for biscuits, chocolates, liqueurs \n </br>
        <br> - Tubes for preserves, creams and cosmetics \n </br>
        <br> - Metal caps, closures and caps for bottles (eg oil, wine, spirits, soft drinks) \n \n </br>
        DO NOT INTRODUCE the YELLOW container: \n \n
        <br> Containers for paints, enamels, stain removers, solvents, acids, glues and insecticides \n \n </br>
        <br> Please note: The labels must not be removed, the packaging must not be washed, to avoid bad smells just rinse them quickly and food residues must be removed </br>
    </string>
    <string name="differenziata6_tit">Metals</string>
    <string name="scopri_di_piu">LEARN MORE!</string>
    <string name="sped_desc_intro">
        Various volunteer groups operate in the Genoese territory that deal with the reclamation of polluted places. \n
        <br> This section has been designed to simplify the organization and inform of the existence of these initiatives. \n \n </br>
        <br> Even if you are not in a volunteer group you will have the opportunity to create an expedition and find people who, like you, care about the cleanliness of our city. \n </br>
        <br> Log in or register now to see shipments that have already been scheduled or schedule one yourself! </br>
    </string>
    <string name="username_lenght">Username cannot be less than 4 characters</string>
    <string name="username_mod">Username has been modified</string>
    <string name="dove_lo_butto2">Where do I throw it?</string>
    <string name="registrati">Sign in</string>
</resources>